<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Infographics &#8211; RaceBridges Studio</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../index.html</link>
	<description>Seeking to Build Bridges</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 21:42:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>10 Clues to Spot Cyber-Bullying</title>
		<link>./../10-clues-to-spot-cyber-bullying/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 21:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infographic&#038;p=3803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The following 10 electronic clues could be signs of cyber-bullying behavior among your students: Posting humiliating or embarrassing memes or other edited images to mock a student on social media Asking a student to take "private" photos or videos and then forwarding to other students Intentionally taking embarrassing photos or videos of a student without [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>10 Reminders to Make a Difference</title>
		<link>./../10-reminders-to-make-a-difference/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 21:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infographic&#038;p=3806</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[From the Powerful Words and Works of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. Citizens of a Global Family Be a part of a vibrant, multi-racial world that seeks justice, peace and reconciliation. Community Builders Strive to strengthen community connections so every race, gender, religion can be part of something bigger. Hope Givers Help the poor and [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>15 Ways to Teach Civility to Children</title>
		<link>./../15-ways-to-teach-civility-to-children/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infograph&#038;p=2914</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Today’s world is more diverse than ever.  People come from many different cultures and upbringings which can result in conflict and misunderstandings.  Children, from a very young age, need to be taught how to challenge differences in a way that is respectful and productive.  Lead by example Think before you act, or speak Be Kind [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be a Mural Maker and Shaper</title>
		<link>./../be-a-mural-maker-and-shaper/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2019 13:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infograph&#038;p=2894</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[8 Ways to Use Murals to Open New Worlds, Share Perspectives and Explore History 1.  Highlight Celebrations or Events Consider a mural project for your school or organization. This could showcase an historical anniversary, some cultural achievements or a special community event. The subject matter a cooperative venture among your student body, staff, volunteers and [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creating a Classroom Diversity Checklist</title>
		<link>./../creating-a-classroom-diversity-checklist/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infograph&#038;p=2917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As this school year comes to an end, teachers around the country take a brief break from the classroom. This summer is a perfect time to reflect on the school year. What went well? What could you do better? How did your students do – did they meet your expectations academically? You know that the [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Icebreakers!</title>
		<link>./../icebreakers/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infograph&#038;p=2916</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Student Groups: Strategies that Facilitate Positive Interactions How many of us have felt uncomfortable approaching someone new to a group we are used to? Unsure of what to say to them? Worry that they may find us strange or abnormal? Concerned that we may not have anything in common with this new person? Students are [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tips for Combating Racism in the Classroom</title>
		<link>./../tips-for-combating-racism-in-the-classroom/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infograph&#038;p=2913</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Write a Commitment Pledge to racial unity at your school or in your class During class discussion, explore the interracial issues and challenges in your school community and in your adjoining neighborhoods.  Create a process where all can contribute in a reflective and honest way to write a Pledge Against Racism for your school.  Have [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why bullying is more dangerous than ever — and what teachers can do to stop it</title>
		<link>./../why-bullying-is-more-dangerous-than-ever-and-what-teachers-can-do-to-stop-it/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 11:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHICS]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../staging/index.html?post_type=infograph&#038;p=2915</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bullying isn’t a new problem. But in recent years, it has outgrown its reputation as an annoyance of childhood and turned into something much more dangerous. And sometimes harder to spot. While physical aggression is on the rise among teens, so is a subtler — but deeply disturbing — form of bullying called relational aggression. [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
