<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>LEADER RESOURCES &#8211; RaceBridges Studio</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>Seeking to Build Bridges</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 01:21:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>10 Ways to Educate for Anti-Racism and to Celebrate Diversity</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/10-ways-to-educate-for-anti-racism-and-to-celebrate-diversity/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:35:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3402</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Classrooms are more than diverse than ever and it's up to everyone to make sure everyone feels welcomed and that racism (or any 'ism) isn't tolerated. This resource provides 10 ideas, tips and tools to build bridges within classrooms but can easily be modified to work within the workplace, organization or any community.]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Culture of Respect Challenges Students to Connect</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/a-culture-of-respect-challenges-students-to-connect/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:16:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3398</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ask any student what the hardest part of school is and the answer will surprise you.  In fact, geometry and physics aren’t even on the list.  Most students state that the most difficult part is learning how to fit in, dealing with students with very diverse backgrounds and experiences, and how to break down social [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Be Civil!</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/be-civil/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 22:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[How can we explore the human skill of . . . Disagreeing Without Being Disagreeable? THE SEARCH FOR CIVILITY Given the increasing volatility of political discourse in the United States, from vitriolic editorializing presented as news to recent Tea Party protests, there is a need for students to learn how to disagree while remaining civil. [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celebrating Women : Bridgebuilders and Storytellers</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/celebrating-women-bridgebuilders-and-storytellers/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3346</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[RaceBridges honors Women’s History Month each year in the month of March. But gender equality is an important diversity issue that can be explored at any time. So we publish here our lesson plan for Women’s History Month in this Resource format. We remember that any time in the school year is a good time [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Create a Welcoming School</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/create-a-welcoming-school/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 22:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3368</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Teachers can do a great deal to make classrooms more welcoming, but it is also important that schools as institutions are inclusive at the “macro” level. This resource offers suggestions to make the entire school a more “accessible” and welcoming place to all students. You might use some of the suggestions below in your classroom, [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Creating a Diversity Session for your Faculty : An Introduction</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/creating-a-diversity-session-for-your-faculty-an-introduction/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3410</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This resource is meant to help administrators, teachers, and staff to: Become more aware of the many facets of diversity Explore their own experiences with diversity Identify the diversity of the school community Value learning about and addressing diversity in the school community Identify how understanding diversity can serve the quality of the school See [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Finding New Words: A Resource for Addressing Bullying at School</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/finding-new-words-a-resource-for-addressing-bullying-at-school/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3350</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[“I get on the bus first thing in the morning and it starts. The name calling…about my mixed race. It’s like I become invisible except for that, except for my skin color. It’s so weird.” – A High School Student “And it just grew and grew and no one was backing down like they said [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Giving it Back: Service Learning in Your Classroom</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/giving-it-back-service-learning-in-your-classroom/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3325</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As every good teacher knows . . . Service Learning combines academic classroom curriculum with meaningful service in the community. It’s a way of teaching, learning and reflecting that aims to enrich the learning experience, teach civic responsibility and encourage lifelong civic engagement. Service Learning builds on students’ abilities and interest in the world around [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Including Everyone: Small Changes to Create a Welcoming Classroom</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/including-everyone-small-changes-to-create-a-welcoming-classroom/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 23:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3394</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Even though we want to make sure that our students learn the skills of anti-racism and are prepared to live in a multi-cultural world, it can be hard to find time to teach explicitly anti-racism lessons or to implement an entire diversity curriculum.  But what we do every day, in regular classroom situations, can have [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Keep the Peace!</title>
		<link>./../../../lesson/keep-the-peace/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 20:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[LEADER RESOURCES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?post_type=lesson&#038;p=3342</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Creating safe, welcoming communities is the job of the entire school—teachers, administrators, staff, and students—but even small changes can make a big difference. This resource suggests some mini-lessons and ideas for “keeping the peace” in your classroom. Purpose To identify causes of bullying, harassment, and/or violence To understand the importance of creating safe, welcoming school [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
