<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>BLOG ARTICLES &#8211; RaceBridges Studio</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>Seeking to Build Bridges</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 01:09:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Be Civil! The Search for Civility</title>
		<link>./../../../be-civil-the-search-for-civility/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 22:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3063</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Definition : “…formal politeness and courtesy in behavior or speech..” Its Use : “I hope we can treat each other with civility and respect” ___________________ “Civility is not something that automatically happens. Civil societies come about because people want them to.” Jimmy Bise, Jr. ___________________ Some claim that civil society is breaking down as [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Columbus or Native Americans: Who are the Real Indigenous Peoples?</title>
		<link>./../../../columbus-or-native-americans-who-are-the-real-indigenous-peoples/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 22:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3069</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Our country honors Christopher Columbus for his discovery of America. When he arrived on its shores, however, there were already people living on the land – Native Americans. Who, then, are the real indigenous people of America? Where do schools and teachers start when teaching this subject to students? Below are a few tips for [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cyber Bullying</title>
		<link>./../../../cyber-bullying/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 20:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3033</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Electronic technology has given rise to a whole new form of bullying – cyber bullying or electronic aggression. Imagine you’re a student being teased by the school bully. You can avoid or get away from him or her, right? Not so in the pervasive electronic world of email, texts, posts and voicemail. 24/7 you can [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Going the Extra Mile in the Classroom: Embracing Cultural Differences</title>
		<link>./../../../going-the-extra-mile-in-the-classroom-embracing-cultural-differences/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 20:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3130</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Exploring ‘Insiders &amp; Outsiders’ with your students or group. In the classroom, it is a fine line to walk. To openly acknowledge the differences and diversity of today’s students without creating an “insider/outsider” situation can be a tricky balancing act of political correctness and acceptance. Every teacher knows this line, and treads lightly. Virtually everyone [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>He Said, She Said: Understanding and Preventing Student Gossip</title>
		<link>./../../../he-said-she-said-understanding-and-preventing-student-gossip/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 21:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3052</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Although difficult to admit, it is quite likely that each of us has engaged in gossip or rumor spreading at some point in our lives. We have all felt the sting of humiliation from gossip when it has been directed at ourselves, and have likely been a party to someone else’s humiliation as well. Words [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Welcoming is Your School Climate?</title>
		<link>./../../../how-welcoming-is-your-school-climate/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 00:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[If we are to achieve a richer culture, rich in contrasting values, we must recognize the whole gamut of human  potentialities, and so we weave a less arbitrary social fabric, one in which each diverse human gift will find a fitting place.          – Margaret Mead There’s a lot that we can do to make [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Boarding Schools &#8211; Part 1 of 4</title>
		<link>./../../../indian-boarding-schools-part-1-of-4/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 21:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3139</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[NOTE: As we take the month of November to celebrate the contributions of the First Nations, we want to witness also the sad truth of attempts at the genocide of the American Indians and their cultures. Particularly, we take this month to focus on the Indian Boarding Schools. We offer these four articles because as [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Boarding Schools &#8211; Part 2 of 4</title>
		<link>./../../../indian-boarding-schools-part-2-of-4/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 21:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3142</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Why is it important that we acknowledge and even study about the existence and the abuses of the Indian Boarding Schools?  We cannot build any kind of future on a foundation of lies. Some children, thank goodness, had some positive experiences at some Boarding Schools. However, the secrecy and manipulation that surrounded the entire initiative [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Boarding Schools &#8211; Part 3 of 4</title>
		<link>./../../../indian-boarding-schools-part-3-of-4/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 21:35:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3150</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On June 11, 2008, millions of Canadians tuned into a live, nationally-television apology to the First Nations from their Prime Minister, Stephen Harper. In this historic speech in the House of Commons, the Canadian government took full responsibility for the Canadian government’s attempts to assimilate First Nations children “causing great harm that has lasted for [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Indian Boarding Schools &#8211; Part 4 of 4</title>
		<link>./../../../indian-boarding-schools-part-4-of-4/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[ecldi]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 21:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[BLOG ARTICLES]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../staging/index.html?p=3153</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[After a century of government policy that forcibly removed tens of thousands of First Nations’ children from their homes and sent them to boarding schools that basically amounted to forced labor camps, The U.S. Congress passed the Indian Child Welfare Act in 1978  (ICWA) to put an end to this and other policies toward American [...]]]></description>
		
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
